// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which part of database holds only one type of information?",
    answer: "Field",
    options: [
      "Report",
      "Field",
      "Record",
      "File"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: ".mov is what kind of extention?",
    answer: "Video",
    options: [
      "Video",
      "Audio",
      "Image",
      "Word"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "int main()\n{\n\tint var = O52;\n\tprintf(\"%d\",var);\n}",
    answer: "42",
    options: [
      "52",
      "60",
      "42",
      "44"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "The first web browser",
    answer: "Nexus",
    options: [
      "Internet Explorer",
      "Mozilla Firefox",
      "Mosaic",
      "Nexus"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "How many layers does OSI model have?",
    answer: "7",
    options: [
      "6",
      "9",
      "7",
      "5"
    ]
  },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

    {
    numb: 6,
    question: ".gif is what kind of extention?",
    answer: "Image",
    options: [
      "Video",
      "Image",
      "Text",
      "Word"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "A folder in Windows computer cannot be created with this name",
    answer: "con",
    options: [
      "mkdir",
      "con",
      "rep",
      "ese"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "How many options are available in facebook to react to a post? ",
    answer: "6",
    options: [
      "7",
      "6",
      "5",
      "4"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which is the virtual assistant of facebook ",
    answer: "M",
    options: [
      "M",
      "Bookme",
      "Cortana",
      "BigB"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Colour of Blackbox",
    answer: "Orange",
    options: [
      "Orange",
      "Black",
      "White",
      "Red"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 11,
    question: "Current stable version of Google",
    answer: "101",
    options: [
      "100",
      "101",
      "102",
      "103"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 12,
    question: "ASCII value of 'A'",
    answer: "65",
    options: [
      "97",
      "67",
      "65",
      "95"
    ]
  },

  
];